onlinecomputerbooks.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy policy : Download Free Book

## Privacy policy

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users of this website based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

OnlineProgrammingBooks.com will not sell your email address to a third party. At no time is personal information collected without explicit consent.

Email subscriptions are managed and delivered by [Google’s Feedburner Service](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). Subscribers and users of the Feedburner service are subject to Google’s terms and privacy policies, you can review their [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) and [TOS](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/terms/) before subscribing by email. OnlineProgrammingBooks.com is not responsible or liable for the actions, service failures, security measures or policies and procedures of Feedburner.com.
